<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Arcane</string>
    <string name="Pit_Compose">
                1. Choose a place to dig. \n\n
                2. Dig a hole 12 inches / 30 cm deep. \n\n
                3. Dump in your food waste into the hole.\n\n
                4. Cover the hole with at least 6 inches / 15 cm of soil. \n\n
                5. Turn the compost once in a while. \n\n
                6. Done ! \n\n
        </string>
    <string name="Vermi_Compose">
                1. Provide an organic waste materials such as vermiworm. \n\n
                2. Prepare a vermi compost bed measuring one meter wide and five meters in length. \n\n
                3. Add the organic waste materials into the compost bed.\n\n
                4. Water the compost bed to make it more mosturized. \n\n
                5. Add one kilogram of earthworm into the bed. \n\n
                6. Put a sacks as a cover on top of the compost bed for a conducive environments for the earthworm. \n\n
                7. After a few months, sieve the harvested vermicast to separate the earthworms with undecomposed materials. \n\n
                8. Done !\n\n
        </string>
    <string name="alternativeText">
        \nUnfortunately, this food category is not suitable for food decomposition technique.\n
        \nYou can dispose the food waste properly or send it to food facility.\n
        \nFood facility will share the food to other people if the food quality is in appropriate condition.\n

    </string>

    <string name="alternativeTextDispose">
        \nYou have chosen to dispose your food waste.\n

        \nMake sure to disposed your food waste responsibly in a garbage bin for collection by your commercial waste service for disposal in landfill.\n
    </string>

    <string name="alternativeTextShare">
        \nShared successfully !\n\n
        \nYour food waste will be pick up by commercial food waste service and will be send to food facility.\n
    </string>

</resources>